

Contact

Phone

+48 571 360 043

Email

wjezierski23@gmail.com

Portfolio

https://wjezierski.com

Github

https://github.com/Wojciech-Jezierski

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/wojciechjezierski-dev

Skills

- HTML
- CSS, SCSS, BEM, CSS Modules
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- · React, Redux
- React-query, react-hook-form, react-router-dom
- Tailwind CSS, Material UI, Styled Components
- REST API, GraphQL API
- End-2-end tests in Cypress
- Firebase, chart.js
- Docker, CI/CD Pipelines (basics)
- NPM, Yarn, ESLint, Husky
- Figma, Adobe XD
- Scrum, Jira
- GIT

Languages

Polish - native

English - upper intermediate (B2)

Wojciech Jezierski

Junior Front-end developer

About me

I'm 23 years old graduate of Computer Science with 6 month of commercial experience. I'm an aspiring front-end developer and creative problem solver with a passion for crafting engaging and user-friendly web interfaces. Proficient in languages like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, they excel at translating design concepts into responsive and visually appealing websites and applications.

Work Experience

O 06.2022 - 10.2022

Northvolt Systems Sp. z o.o.

Front-end developer (internship)

- Develop front-end parts of Manufacturing Execution System (MES) in Vue.js library
- Creation of responsive views to be reused in multiple systems
- Displaying data on a chart using the Chart.js library and the Vue.js framework
- Raporting in Jira
- Cooperation in the scrum methodology in an international team

Technologies: Vue.js, Chart.js, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, HTML, CSS, Jira

O5.2021 - 08.2021

SBKY

Front-end developer (practice)

- UX/UI prototyping of a web application
- Creating websites in Wordpress
- Selection and configuration of appropriate wordpress plugins

Technologies: PHP, Wordpress, Figma, Adobe XD

Completed projects

HR Dashboard (Mentoring Reskilled - https://reskilled.io/)

- A platform for HR teams to collect data on candidates applying for specific positions.
- The project was written in TypeScript and the React framework, which uses hooks.
- The application has a full CRUD including JWT tokens and the API has documentation in Swagger.
- Tailwind was used for UI styling, Yup was used for form validation, React Hook Form was used for form handling, Axios and React Query were used for API communication.
- Additional GET Endpoint as JSON object was mockup in designer.mocky.io.
- Employee of month displayed through graphql-request and react-query libraries.
- Functionality has been tested using end-2-end tests in Cypress.
- The project was carried out under the guidance of a senior software engineer. I worked on multiple branches, the application was divided into tasks, which were subjected to senior code review.

Live track app (engineering project)

 An application for speditors, developed using firebase platform, google maps API, react framework and SCSS.

Expense tracker

 Application for expense tracker build in plain JavaScript and React using hooks(UseState, useContext, useReducer) and the context API.

Education

O 03.2023 - Present

WSB University in Gdańsk

Menagement of IT projects and services

Degree: Master of Science

0 10.2019 - 02.2023

WSB University in Gdańsk

Computer Science

Degree: Bachelor of Engineering

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).